This file belongs to quickheal – it’s a log file!! Please do not rename, delete or modify this file.

Quick Heal Technologies Ltd. is one of the leading IT security solutions company. Each Quick Heal product is designed to simplify IT security management across the length and depth of devices and on multiple platforms. They are customized to suit consumers, small businesses, Government establishments and corporate houses.

Over a span of 3 decades the company's R&D has focused on computer and network security solutions. The current portfolio of cloud-based security and advanced machine learning enabled solutions stop threats, attacks and malicious traffic before it strikes.